We got a nice looking application we added a lot of functionality over the last lectures,
Mamy adnie wygldajc aplikacj, dodalimy wiele funkcjonalnoci podczas ostatnich wykadw.
now of course we want to have a really good application not only by the looks of it but also by the
Teraz oczywicie chcemy mie naprawd dobr aplikacj nie tylko pod wzgldem wygldu, ale take sposobu, w
way we structure it,
jaki j tworzymy.
we work with it. Now throughout building this application,
Pracujemy z tym teraz od budowania tej aplikacji.
I already showed you a lot of best practices for building that, I shared my thought process on how to
Pokazaem ju wam wiele dobrych praktyk do budowania, e podzieliem si moim procesem mylowym,
structure and plan the application and I gave you some alternatives at some points of time on how you may
jak zorganizowa i zaplanowa aplikacj, a w niektrych momentach podaem wam rne
split something into components.
sposoby dzielenia czego na komponenty.
Here we actually have a relatively granular component structure,
Tutaj mamy waciwie ziarnist struktur komponentw.
you could certainly combine some of the components we're using
Z pewnoci moesz poczy niektre z komponentw, ktrych uywamy.
but can you also improve some things.
Ale czy moesz poprawi niektre rzeczy.
Let's dive into two important things we learned about, prop types and pure components.
Przeanalizujmy dwie wane rzeczy, ktrych nauczylimy si o typach Propp i czystych komponentach.
So in shouldComponentUpdate
Tak wic krtka aktualizacja skadnika.
and let's also have a look at all these lifecycle methods you learned about in general.
Przyjrzyjmy si take wszystkim tym metodom cyklu ycia, o ktrych si uczysz.
Do we use them in there?
Czy uywamy ich tam.
Why don't we use them at any point right now? Where would we use them?
Dlaczego nie wykorzystamy ich teraz, gdzie bymy z nich korzystali?
Let's answer these questions over the next lectures.
Odpowiedzmy na te pytania podczas kolejnych wykadw.